(Penny:)So, what's the deal
with your apartment?
(Penny:)Why's it taking so long?
(Amy:)Um, it was a drywall problem.
(Penny:)Oh, no, what happened?
(Amy:)Well, the drywall got wet,
and you do not want wet drywall
(Amy:)because when drywall gets
wet, it's really more...
(Penny:)Wet wall?
(Amy:)Or damp wall, just as bad.
Mm.
(Penny:)So why don't they
just get more drywall?
(Amy:)Well, they went to get some,
(Amy:)but the woman at the wall store
(Amy:)said it was going on sale
and they should wait
(Amy:)because the savings...
Okay, are you done?
(Penny:)Bernadette told me
your apartment's ready.
(Amy:)I was done at wet wall,
but you wouldn't let it go.
(Penny:)But is Sheldon really
believing all this crap?
(Amy:)Well, he started to question it,
but then I fake sneezed on him
(Amy:)and he ran to take a shower.
(Amy:)Please don't say anything,
I feel terrible about this.